<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>technical on n0c7urn3</title>
    <link>/categories/technical/</link>
    <description>Recent content in technical on n0c7urn3</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2019 n0c7urn3 :: Powered by Hugo :: Theme made by panr  ::  The views expressed here are my own and do not reflect those of my past, present, or future employers</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/technical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bachelor&#39;s Degree Capstone Project:  Incident Response Plan part 3</title>
      <link>/posts/2020-01-04-ir-plan3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020-01-04-ir-plan3/</guid>
      <description>Section 3: Network Security Incident Response is merely a piece of the puzzle when looking at the larger picture of network security. Each piece of a defensive strategy should complement and be complemented by each other piece. No piece should be isolated, and no piece should represent a single point of failure. Incident Response is no different, and is dependent upon the strategies that come before it, and informs those that come after.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bachelor&#39;s Degree Capstone Project:  Incident Response Plan part 2</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-12-12-ir-plan2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 17:12:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-12-12-ir-plan2/</guid>
      <description>The following is part 2 of the Incident Response Plan that I submitted as my final capstone project for my BS in CyberSecurity at Colorado Technical University, and was originally written March 18, 2018. I decided to publish it to demonstrate the work I&amp;rsquo;ve done, as well as in the hope that someone will get some benefit from it.
 Section 2: Data Governance Every organization should abide by a data governance program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bachelor&#39;s Degree Capstone Project:  Incident Response Plan part 1</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-11-27-ir-plan1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 07:55:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-11-27-ir-plan1/</guid>
      <description>The following is part 1 of the Incident Response Plan that I submitted as my final capstone project for my BS in CyberSecurity at Colorado Technical University, and was originally written March 18, 2018. I decided to publish it to demonstrate the work I&amp;rsquo;ve done, as well as in the hope that someone will get some benefit from it.
 Abstract The role of incident response at any organization is an important one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 Days of Code</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-05-19-100-days-of-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 08:46:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-05-19-100-days-of-code/</guid>
      <description>I have decided to take part in #100daysofcode (as a start). I intend to work my way through the curriculum at FreeCodeCamp, in part because they offer fairly comprehensive web development courses, and in part because they get you in contact with non-profits to donate your time and skills, and I want to do good in the world. Yes, I do want the ability to add these items to my portfolio, but I want so badly to work on something I can believe in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hardening</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-05-03-hardening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 08:28:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-05-03-hardening/</guid>
      <description>I will not purport to be an expert on hardening systems, especially since this is really my first attempt to do so. I know I&amp;rsquo;ve done a bit more than some, especially since alot of people just use the default and they&amp;rsquo;re done. I also know I&amp;rsquo;ve probably got quite a bit more I can do.
The first thing I did (which really should not have been the first thing I did, as you&amp;rsquo;ll see my order to be a bit flawed on priority) was to install and enable an SSL certificate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up My Site From Scratch</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-05-02-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 17:54:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-05-02-site/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve made a few websites in the past: A website called Newb Sec that I and a friend were going to use as a blog together (that would have satisfied many of the goals for this website), and a website for a residential computer repair business that I was trying to start as a means to try to transition into working for myself (which was misconceived for the amount of time I actually had to dedicate to it, working a full time job as is, and going to school full time).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scoreboard</title>
      <link>/scoreboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/scoreboard/</guid>
      <description>TEAM CTFs
   Team Host Date Rank/Score/Completion     DeadPixels The Many Hats Club - Hack The Box Dec 2019 550, 18th place    SOLO CTFs
   Host Date Rank/Score/Completion      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>